http://vutec.com/vutec-projector-screens-privacy-policy/

Vutec Projector Screens Privacy Policy - Vutec Projector Screens | Projector Screen Excellence
Fixed
Eleganté Vu-Easy Projector Screens Stiletto Projector Screen
Motorized
Lectric 3 Projector Screens Lectric 3 C Projector Screen Lectric 3 X Projector Screens Lectric 3 RF Projector Screens Lectric 3 FD Projector Screens Lectric 4 Projector Screens Lectric 4 C MDF Projector Screens Lectric 4 X Projector Screens
Portable
Retracta-Vu Traveller Projector Lift
Silverstar™
Silverstar Classic Standard Wall Mount Projector Screen Silverstar Extensive Wall Mount Projector Screen Silverstar Slimline Wall Mount Projector Screen
Vision X™
Vision X Motorized Vision X Fixed Vision X Curved
Artscreen™ Systems
Types Licensed Artwork Frames & Liners Artscreen Designer FAQ
Theater Art Systems™Screen SurfacesAccessories
Frames & Liners Licensed Artwork Control Devices Projector Lifts Screen Installation Accessories Screens Installation InstructionsResourcesDealer
Become a Dealer Dealer Portal Magnolia PortalBuyContact UsBlog
Search for:
Menu Close
About UsVutec Brands Vutec
Fixed
Eleganté Vu-Easy Projector Screens Stiletto Projector Screen
Motorized
Lectric 3 Projector Screens Lectric 3 C Projector Screen Lectric 3 X Projector Screens Lectric 3 RF Projector Screens Lectric 3 FD Projector Screens Lectric 4 Projector Screens Lectric 4 C MDF Projector Screens Lectric 4 X Projector Screens
Portable
Retracta-Vu Traveller Projector Lift
Silverstar™
Silverstar Classic Standard Wall Mount Projector Screen Silverstar Extensive Wall Mount Projector Screen Silverstar Slimline Wall Mount Projector Screen
Vision X™
Vision X Motorized Vision X Fixed Vision X Curved
Artscreen™ Systems
Types Licensed Artwork Frames & Liners Artscreen Designer FAQ
Theater Art Systems™Screen SurfacesAccessories Frames & Liners Licensed Artwork Control Devices Projector Lifts Screen Installation Accessories Screens Installation InstructionsResourcesDealer Become a Dealer Dealer Portal Magnolia PortalBuyContact UsBlog
Privacy Policy
Thank you for using our Website. This statement discloses the privacy policy and describes how your personal information is collected, used, and shared when you visit or make a purchase from Vutec’s website, vutec.com (the “Site”).We have adopted this Privacy Policy to further the relationship between us and the users of the Site. This statement of our Privacy Policy makes disclosures concerning our collection of information, including personal information, when you use the Site, and how we use and disclose it to others. By using the Site you accept the practices described in this Privacy Policy, as well as any applicable Terms of Use found on Site or other applicable policies.Information We CollectWhen you visit the Site, we automatically collect certain information about your device, including information about your web browser, IP address, time zone, and some of the cookies that are installed on your device. Additionally, as you browse the Site, we collect information about the individual web pages or products that you view, what websites or search terms referred you to the Site, and information about how you interact with the Site. We refer to this automatically-collected information as “Device Information.”We collect Device Information using the following technologies:– “Cookies” are data files that are placed on your device or computer and often include an anonymous unique identifier. For more information about cookies, and how to disable cookies, visit http://www.allaboutcookies.org.– “Log files” track actions occurring on the Site, and collect data including your IP address, browser type, Internet service provider, referring/exit pages, and date/time stamps.– “Web beacons,” “tags,” and “pixels” are electronic files used to record information about how you browse the Site.Additionally when you make a purchase or attempt to make a purchase through the Site, we collect certain information from you, including your name, billing address, shipping address, payment information (including credit card numbers, email address, and phone number. We refer to this information as “Order Information.”When we talk about “Personal Information” in this Privacy Policy, we are talking both about Device Information and Order Information.Our Use of Information for Internal PurposeWe use your personal information primarily for our own internal purposes, such as providing, maintaining, evaluating, and improving our Site and the products and services we offer and to provide you with requested information related to our products, education, seminars, events, and other information you may request from time to time. Our collection of your salon and cosmetology license number ensures that we are providing information available only to industry professionals.We use the non-personal information we collect to track the use of the Site and to assist us in providing, maintaining, evaluating, and improving our Site and the services and products we offer and sell.How Do We Use Your Personal Information?We use your personal information primarily for our own internal purposes, such as providing, maintaining, evaluating, and improving our Site and the products and services we offer and to provide you with requested information related to our products, education, seminars, events, and other information you may request from time to time. We use the non-personal information we collect to track the use of the Site and to assist us in providing, maintaining, evaluating, and improving our Site and the services and products we offer and sell.We use the Order Information that we collect generally to fulfill any orders placed through the Site (including processing your payment information, arranging for shipping, and providing you with invoices and/or order confirmations). Additionally, we use this Order Information to:Communicate with you;Screen our orders for potential risk or fraud; andWhen in line with the preferences you have shared with us, provide you with information or advertising relating to our products or services.We use the Device Information that we collect to help us screen for potential risk and fraud (in particular, your IP address), and more generally to improve and optimize our Site (for example, by generating analytics about how our customers browse and interact with the Site, and to assess the success of our marketing and advertising campaigns).Email marketing (if applicable): With your permission, we may send you emails about our store, new products and other updates.Advertising (if applicable): We use online advertising to show you other products that we sell.Our Disclosure of Personal Information to Third PartiesWe will disclose your personal information to protect or enforce our legal rights and policies, to protect or enforce the legal rights of a third party, or as we in good faith believe we are required to do so by law (e.g., to comply with a subpoena or court order).We may contract with various third parties who help us provide, maintain and improve the Site and the services we provide and the services and products we offer and sell and such third parties may have access to your personal information in order to perform their services. We may contract with third parties to help us manage, monitor and optimize our Site and the services and products we offer and sell. We may also use third party contractors to help us measure the effectiveness of our advertising and communications. We will enter into confidentiality and non-disclosure agreements with all third parties that have access to your personal information which will prohibit them from using or disclosing your personal information except for the purpose of providing services to use. We intend to take commercially reasonable steps to enforce such non-disclosure and confidentiality agreements if and when we become aware of any violations.We share your Personal Information with third parties to help us use your Personal Information, as described above. For example, we use Shopify to power our online store for our dealers –you can read more about how Shopify uses your Personal Information here: https://www.shopify.com/legal/privacy. We use woocommerce for our online consumer store, — you can read more about how WooCommerce uses your Personal Information here: https://woocommerce.com/privacy-policy/ .We also use Google Analytics to help us understand how our customers use the Site–you can read more about how Google uses your Personal Information here: https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/. You can also opt-out of Google Analytics here: https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.Finally, we may also share your Personal Information to comply with applicable laws and regulations, to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other lawful request for information we receive, or to otherwise protect our rights.Behavioral AdvertisingAs described above, we use your Personal Information to provide you with targeted advertisements or marketing communications we believe may be of interest to you. For more information about how targeted advertising works, you can visit the Network Advertising Initiative’s (“NAI”) educational page at http://www.networkadvertising.org/understanding-online-advertising/how-does-it-work.You can opt out of targeted advertising by:FACEBOOK – https://www.facebook.com/settings/?tab=adsGOOGLE – https://www.google.com/settings/ads/anonymousBING – https://advertise.bingads.microsoft.com/en-us/resources/policies/personalized-adsAdditionally, you can opt out of some of these services by visiting the Digital Advertising Alliance’s opt-out portal at: http://optout.aboutads.info/.Do Not TrackPlease note that we do not alter our Site’s data collection and use practices when we see a Do Not Track signal from your browser.Your RightsIf you are a European resident, you have the right to access personal information we hold about you and to ask that your personal information be corrected, updated, or deleted. If you would like to exercise this right, please contact us through the contact information below.Additionally, if you are a European resident we note that we are processing your information in order to fulfill contracts we might have with you (for example if you make an order through the Site), or otherwise to pursue our legitimate business interests listed above. Additionally, please note that your information will be transferred outside of Europe, including to Canada and the United States.Data RetentionWhen you place an order through the Site, we will maintain your Order Information for our records unless and until you ask us to delete this information.MinorsThe Site is not intended for individuals under the age of 13.Our Use of CookiesA cookie is a small file placed on the hard drive of your computer. Most websites use cookies. We will use cookies to track your use of the Site and the services and products we offer and sell and also to provide you with a more personalized user experience. We do not and can not use cookies to retrieve personal information from your computer.How We Protect Your Personal InformationWe consider protecting the security of your personal information as very important. When you enter personal information, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (sometimes referred to as “SSL”).We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we do not guarantee absolute security. We are not responsible for the unauthorized acts of others and we assume no liability for any disclosure of information due to errors in transmission, unauthorized third party access (such as through hacking) or other acts of third parties, or acts or omissions beyond our reasonable control.ChangesWe may update this privacy policy from time to time in order to reflect, for example, changes to our practices or for other operational, legal or regulatory reasons.Contact UsFor more information about our privacy practices, if you have questions, or if you would like to make a complaint, please contact us by e-mail at marketing@vutec.com or by mail using the details provided below:Vutec Corporation11711 W Sample RdCoral Springs FL 33065USAThis Privacy Policy was last updated May, 2018.
ResourcesNewsBecome a DealerWarranty & ReturnsOnlineTCPrivacy PolicyArchitect ResourcesFAQ’sArtscreen FAQContactWhere to Buy
© Copyright Vutec Corporation 2020
This website uses cookies to improve your experience. If you continue, you accept our privacy policy .AcceptReject Read MorePrivacy & Cookies Policy
Close
Privacy Overview
This website uses cookies to improve your experience while you navigate through the website. Out of these cookies, the cookies that are categorized as necessary are stored on your browser as they are essential for the working of basic functionalities of the website. We also use third-party cookies that help us analyze and understand how you use this website. These cookies will be stored in your browser only with your consent. You also have the option to opt-out of these cookies. But opting out of some of these cookies may have an effect on your browsing experience.
Necessary
Necessary
Always Enabled
Necessary cookies are absolutely essential for the website to function properly. This category only includes cookies that ensures basic functionalities and security features of the website. These cookies do not store any personal information.
Non-necessary
Non-necessary
Any cookies that may not be particularly necessary for the website to function and is used specifically to collect user personal data via analytics, ads, other embedded contents are termed as non-necessary cookies. It is mandatory to procure user consent prior to running these cookies on your website.
Translate »
